(PHONE RlNGlNG)
OPERATOR:
Vancouver Court Hotel,
how may I help you?
Hello, Vancouver,
this is Michael Scott
calling from
the United States of America.
l have a reservation
in your fair city
from February 1 2th
to the 1 9th.
First week of the Olympics.
Well, we're looking forward
to having you,
so let me just pull up
your information here.
Oki-doke.
Uh, l don't seem
to have it, sir.
What?
l'm not seeing anything
under confirmation. . .
No. No.
Could it be under
"affirmation?"
'Cause you have
thousands of those.
We're just trying to
look it up right now.
You did get the
e-vite to my barbeque.
Come on, Dwight.
Michael.
OPERATOR: Sir, a Iot of
people are trying to get
Iast-minute reservations
at hoteIs here
for the OIympics,
but we've been
fully booked for months.
Well, l have been
booked for three years,
so you should have that.
l have always heard
that British Columbia
is a very nice place,
but l'm not getting that
from this conversation.
Wait, l got it!
Confirmation code,
X-V-2-R-D-M.
Oh.
Here it is. Yeah.
OPERATOR: Uh-huh.
Thank you.
Seven nights
in our street-view
economy single.
That's it.
Yeah.
We changed systems
a whiIe back.
I do apologize.
Okay.
(STAMMERS) How may I
heIp you, Mr. Scott?
All right.
l would like to cancel
my reservation, please.
There is a canceIIation fee
for this, sir.
Okay, put it on my card.
MlCHAEL: Today, Jo Bennett,
the CEO from Sabre
is coming to see us
here for the first time.
She bought us sight unseen,
like a mail-order bride,
(CHUCKLES) so she's
gotta be kind of nervous.
I mean, are we ugly?
Are we smart? Are we cooI?
Are we too cooI?
(BARKlNG)
Do we speak English?
(JO LAUGHlNG)
Why, hello!
GABE: This is
Michael Scott,
co-regional manager
of this branch.
Pleasure to meet you,
Miss Bennett.
Uh, that's Mrs. Bennett,
sweetheart.
My husband and l are
divorced but l kept
the "missus"
just to piss off
the new wife.
Oh.
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
Well, let's take a gander
around this place.
These sure are
pretty dogs.
JO: (CHUCKLlNG)
They love a good crotch.
They sure do.
You should take that
as a compliment.
Oh, l do.
JO: Hello.
Hello.
Do you always stay
seated when a lady
enters the room?
l am treating you
the same as a man,
for whom l would
also not stand.
Unless it was
the president,
or Judge Judy.
l like that.
GABE: This is Accounting.
JO: Uh-huh.
Hi.
Good-looking group.
Over here is
Meredith Palmer,
Creed Bratton.
JO: Another couple
of heartbreakers.
Who's this tall
drink of sun tea?
That is Jim Halpert.
He is the co-regional manager
of this office.
l thought this guy
was the manager.
Oh, he is.
He's the co-manager.
That's the other co-manager.
Two guys doing one job?
We gotta do something
about that. (CHUCKLlNG)
l've got some
Valentine's cards
for my co-workers
and my bro-workers.
No. No.
What? No candy?
ANDY: Valentine's Day.
Right around the corner.
Erin and l have been
on zero dates.
So l got her a
Valentine's Day card,
but I didn't want
to seem too eager,
so I got cards for
everyone in the
whoIe office
to kind of diIute
it a IittIe bit.
Look alive.
(EXCLAlMS)
Jeez, you gave me
a paper cut on my throat.
Yeah, l have this thing
about men cutting
or threatening
to cut my throat.
Don't try to
cut my throat.
Jo, l don't know how
things work in Florida,
which from your description
sounds like a colorful,
lawless swamp,
but here it takes
two men to do one job,
where in Florida,
it might take
one very strong
woman to do such a job.
Whoa. Whoa.
l'll take over.
Um, what we're
doing here,
Michael handles
more of the big
picture stuff,
and l handle more of
the day-to-day stuff.
Yeah.
JlM: So, together. . .
l think l understand.
All right.
Each of you is
doing half a job.
No.
(CHUCKLES) And sometimes
l can hardly handle that.
(JO CHUCKLlNG)
Now this is knucklehead talk.
l'm not going to abide it,
you know.
You can't give me gravy
and tell me it's jelly,
'cause gravy ain't sweet.
ls it, Jim?
(SOFTLY)
l don't think so.
Michael?
Forget the question.
l think one of you
should return to Sales,
and the other one
will be a manager.
l humbly accept
the management position.
Why would you just
automatically get it?
Because, well, Jim,
where l'm from, there
are two types of folk,
those who ain't and those
who are knee-high on
a grasshopper.
Which type ain't you ain't?
Y'all come back now.
Do you even know
what that means?
Yes.
Well, l'm gonna
let this marinate.
So you can go.
Um. . .
You can go on.
Yeah.
(SHOOlNG)
l'm Jolene Bennett,
Jo for short. l'm
a breast cancer survivor,
close personal friends
with Nancy Pelosi,
and Truman Capote
and I slept with three
of the same guys.
When l was a little girl,
l was terrified to fly,
and now I have my
own pilot's license.
l am CEO of
Sabre lnternational
and l sell the best damn
printers and all-in-one
machines Korea can make.
Pleased to meet you.
(EXCLAlMS) Traffic jam.
Uh-oh. Traffic jam
on route three.
(BOTH lMlTATlNG
HORN HONKlNG)
Twenty people
dead in a pileup.
There's blood everywhere.
Um, l got you
a Valentine's card.
You did?
Yeah.
(EXCLAlMS) A bird and a dog !
Yeah, well,
it's Snoopy
and Woodstock.
You named them?
Uh, Charles Schulz did.
l thought it was relevant
'cause l got you all
those birds for Christmas,
remember?
Yeah, l do remember.
Oh, they love each other.
Oh, look at that.
They sure do.
l hadn't noticed.
Oh, it smells
really good, too.
Yeah, it's
Roger Federer for Men.
l sprayed
some in there.
Andy, whoa!
Thank you very much.
lt's got pheromones
in it. (CHUCKLES)
JO: Hey.
KEVlN: Hi.
Just choosing seats,
not getting married.
Chop, chop, little onion.
Jo, there's books
in my chair.
That's right, darling.
Now you're
the proud new owner
of a Sabre handbook,
and my autobiography.
Now, you all must be
in a tizzy. l can see
it on your faces.
l mean, what's going on now?
l mean, who owns
Dunder Mifflin?
Right? l mean, Sabre?
What's that?
Some company
we never heard of from
down in Tallahassee?
l mean, where is that?
Near Mars?
No, we know. Texas.
Now, Dunder Mifflin
has an arm's reach
into all these
small businesses
all over the northeast,
and now we're gonna
take that arm
and we're going to
start selling printers.
l could manage my
way around that.
They're the easiest-to-use
printers in the market.
l will try to
manage my excitement.
l have been saying
the word "manager" a lot,
so whenever Jo
thinks manager,
she thinks of me.
Camel cigarettes
did the same thing
with Joe Camel
by making him
look like a penis.
l can't even go
near a cigarette now
without thinking of
a penis, and vice versa.
l think that's it.
So we're all good.
Okay.
Thanks, y'all.
Oh, my God.
l guess Andy likes me.
l never thought
of him in that way.
But l guess in most
romantic comedies,
the guy you're
supposed to be
with is the one
that you never
thought of in that way.
You might have even thought
he was annoying or
possibly homosexual.
So check this out.
According to the handbook,
you could make more money
as a salesman
than as a manager.
They have all these
incentive programs.
l ran your numbers
from last year.
This is way more
than l make now.
l don't think
l'm gonna miss
being manager.
You know how some people
say they're not in it
for the money?
Well, with all due
respect to this job,
l think l'm definitely
in it for the money.
And, quite honestly,
the women.
Hey. Got a second?
Sure.
All right.
You here to tell me
that you think l would
be a better manager,
and that you are sorry
for being such a jerk?
Actually, yeah.
What?
Exactly that.
l think that you absolutely
deserve the manager position
more than l do.
What? Really?
Yeah.
(LAUGHlNG) Wow! Wow!
(VOCALlZlNG)
Hello, Oscar.
Michael, reading.
What are you reading?
The AtIantic.
Oh, that is
my favorite ocean.
l love it.
l'm so happy right now.
No, l can't keep it
a secret any longer.
Jim's stepping
down to salesman.
l am going to be
the sole manager
once again.
(SlGHS) l should step
into Sales myself.
Why? ls there an
untapped gay market?
Sabre has no caps
on commissions.
He can make a lot
more money in Sales.
(SlGHlNG)
(CLlCKS TONGUE)
Where did you get
that information?
Manual.
Manuel who?
Mmm-hmm.
Well, according to
the manual,
there is no cap
on commissions.
l have been hustled.
(SOFTLY) Son of a bitch.
JlM: This is. . .
Pardon me.
Speak of the devil.
We were just
talking about you.
Have a seat.
Okay.
Now, Jim here is thinking
about taking himself
out of the running
for being manager.
Yep.
Oh, really?
(EXCLAlMS) That is
so sweet of you !
But l cannot accept,
because l have been
thinking about it,
and l think l want
to go back to Sales.
Really?
JlM: Really?
Yeah, you can take the man
out of the salesman,
but you can't take
the sales out of salesman.
Well, l think you're both
being a little too modest.
No, l really, really
think Michael is better
at being manager
for so many reasons.
Mmm-mmm.
No. l think l would be bad.
l would sleep in my office. . .
JO: Okay.
. . .and l would
sexually harass people.
Why would you do that?
l'm turning myself
in right now.
You know, Michael,
you have more experience
in sales and management,
so l'm going to defer
to your judgment.
Thank you.
l think you will
become the salesman,
and congratulations,
you're gonna be
the new manager
of this branch.
That's great.
Congratulations.
Have fun signing my
commission checks, boss.
(EXCLAlMS)
Michael marked his heights.
He's grown.
(BOTH LAUGHlNG)
Bobcat, this is Dragon.
Listen, he's been promoted
to sole manager.
We have got to step
this up. Meet me behind
the dumpster in 90 seconds.
Eighty-nine, 88. . .
You're 20 minutes late.
Um, l was
at another dumpster.
Just admit you
lost track of time.
(SlGHS)
DWlGHT: Ryan and I have been
meeting up to work on our
diabolical plot against Jim.
Ryan is always late
for our meetings.
l wish l had a lair.
Did you see Saw?
Of course l seesaw.
Mose and l seesaw
all the time.
No, the movie.
Did you see
the movie Saw?
Oh. Yeah. Great film.
Almost as fun as
going on a seesaw.
Okay. The reason these
movies are so popular. . .
Mmm-hmm.
. . .is the element of
psychological torment.
l like where you're
going with this.
Continue.
Could we lure him
into an old warehouse
or something?
l have an old barn.
lt's kind of smelly.
Yes.
But that might be a plus.
And then what?
Okay.
We do what they
did in Saw.
l mean, we don't
kill him, obviously.
l have a mask.
Okay, that's your idea?
Exactly like in the movie?
That is the most
idiotic thing l have
ever heard in my life.
Well, suggest something
else then. Don't just. . .
Are you supposed
to cut his leg off?
Don't just
criticize my idea!
Think!
You think of
something then.
Michael, l'm worried that
not all your toys are gonna
fit on your new desk.
How is that possible?
Well, in your old office,
there were all those ledges
and extra space.
No excuses, Erin, come on.
Make it happen.
You know, l actually
think that l should
get back to work.
Jim asked me to
do some stuff,
and he's manager.
Oh, yeah, fine, fine.
Leave it here.
Okay. All right.
MlCHAEL: l have to make
some sales anyway.
Who should l call
with my magic
sales fingers?
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
Michael Scott,
Head of Sales.
You gotta do
something, man.
You can't just sit there.
The new lT guy. Nick.
Nick.
l think he's the key.
He's very trusting.
He's looking for friends.
He's been given
an awesome amount
of power,
and does not know
how to wield it.
Like Frodo.
Why don't you just let me
handle the Tolkien references,
okay, dumb jock?
Well, l think
he can be corrupted.
Like Gollum.
Smeagol was corrupted
and became Gollum.
l might start
a diabolical plot
against him after this one.
Who's hungry?
What is that?
lt's ants on a log.
Michael would always have me
bring them in at 2:30
and say, "Who's hungry?"
(CHUCKLES) Oh. l'm fine.
Thank you, though.
Do you want me to
spin you in your chair
and make you dizzy?
Why would l
want to do that?
lt's a thinking technique.
All the top executives
do it.
lt keeps the brain moving,
and a spinning brain's
a working brain.
For now l'm just gonna
go back to work here.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, thank you.
Well. . .
lt will be a pleasure
doing business with you.
Thanks. Bye, bye.
l just got a new account.
The gentlemen's club
in Carbondale.
lt is called Curves.
l went by there
the other day,
saw some of
the women walking in.
Not really my cup of tea.
Actually, Kevin,
you might like it.
Nice.
You know, we really
don't announce out loud
our sales that much.
Why not? lt's part of
the sales experience.
lt's not really
1 992 anymore.
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
MlCHAEL: Okay.
"You brighten my day
with the sound of
your voice.
"You bring so much
laughter and love.
You're everything to me,
"and l was so blessed
when God sent
you here to me."
(CHUCKLES) Jeez Louise.
l know.
Obsessed with me much?
Well, everyone got one.
What did yours say?
"Friends are worth sharing
a dog house with."
lt's no wonder
that Andy gave Kelly
such a romantic card.
l can't
compete with her.
That girl can sing
and dance and gets all of
her clothes at the mall.
And l feel like such a fool
for thinking that Andy was
only going after one girl,
because Andy Bernard
is a playboy.
And why shouldn't he be?
He's got it all.
(EXCLAlMS)
There he is.
The lT guy.
l see you discovered
the break room.
Yep.
l imagine one of
the best things about
being an lT guy is,
you get to know everyone's
computer passwords.
No, l actually don't.
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
Listen, l know you
have to say that,
but we got
a little problem here.
There is an employee
named Jim Halpert,
and he's doing some
terrible things. Okay?
He's molesting people
via the lnternet,
and we need to stop him.
l think that you
should call the cops.
No, the cops called us.
So l'm gonna need you
to give me the password
to Jim Halpert's computer.
l don't know
what to tell you, man.
l'm sorry.
l just can't give out
his password like that.
Nick, we can make things
very difficult for you.
Are you threatening me?
Threatening you?
No.
(GRUNTS)
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
What is that smell?
Do you smell that?
What is that?
Like a sulfur deposit
under here?
Michael, stop.
No, l'm serious.
We don't have to put up. . .
(SOFTLY) ls it the dogs?
Michael.
You know what?
We don't have to
deal with this.
l am going to
google sulfur maps.
Michael, it's Phyllis.
No, this is geological.
l sent an email
out to everyone
in this area
that this might be
a side effect
to my new allergy
medication l'm on.
Are you kidding me?
No.
And you guys are
okay with this?
She sent an email.
PHYLLlS: l did.
lt's not 'cause
of the smell.
l'm just expecting
a nose bleed.
Oh, my God.
(LAUGHS)
You scared me.
l'm sorry.
l thought you saw me.
l didn't see you.
And you were there
all along.
Well, warmed it up for you,
so it should be good to go.
Cool. Thanks.
Bye, Andy.
That was weird.
No, it ain't.
We all saw the valentine
you gave her.
l don't even know
what that card said.
Believe me,
if l got that card,
we'd be in the bathroom
doing it right now.
(EXCLAlMS)
Hey.
You know, it's funny.
l used to stand in here
and wish l was out there.
Now l'm out there,
and l wish l was in here.
Well, the grass
is always greener.
Yeah, except there's
no grass out there.
lt's just a farty dirt-patch.
Well, it's what
you wanted.
l really need my job back.
We made a terrible
mistake here.
For the record,
l fought this.
All right?
And now, l'm not
really sure what we do.
We make a poster that says,
"Happy Opposite Day"
and she sees it
on the way out.
That's stupid.
Oh, l wish we had one of
those amnesia flashlights
from Men In Black.
Hey. What was that movie
where their boss was
within earshot
and they could have
just gone and talked
to her?
Lethal Weapon?
That's it.
l think we should do it
the LethaI Weapon way.
You two are grown-assed men.
What do l have to do?
Fire you and get
two people in here
who don't need so
much management?
Ah !
(COUGHS) What l. . .
Michael's saying
that he's better
at being a manager,
and l agree.
l'm just. . .
He's a better
people person, weirdly.
And weirdly,
l'm a good dog person,
right, guys?
Come on. See?
They love me.
Fine. l don't care
which one of you
does which job,
just stop meeting with me
to talk about it.
(DOGS PANTlNG)
All right.
(CELL PHONE RlNGlNG)
Oh.
l gotta take this.
Yeah. Finish walking
my dogs for me.
And don't ride them.
A lot of people
try to ride them.
Excuse me, everyone,
please check your emails.
l just sent you
the following message,
"Coworkers,
you may have received
a valentine from me.
"Please understand this
does not mean that
l like you in any way."
You don't even
like us as friends?
Phyllis, you guys are,
like, my closest friends.
l just mean l don't
like-like you.
What are we, five?
"Please don't read
into this card.
"Yours in professionalism,
Nard Dog."
Um, why did l just receive
a mass email from you
that said that
you don't like me?
Do you realize
how hard that makes me
like you, Andy?
lt's not. . . That wasn't. . .
l like someone else.
Who?
(STUTTERS)
lt's not. . .
Whether or not. . .
(MUMBLlNG)
Who? What?
Yeah, l guess Andy
never liked Kelly.
How about that?
(BREATHlNG DEEPLY)
lt smells good in here.
lt sure does. Okay,
we have your space heater,
your humidifier,
your dehumidifier,
your fan, your foot fan
and your food dehydrator.
Erin, what about
my keyboard?
(MUSlC PLAYlNG ON KEYBOARD)
Ah.
So good to be home.
How about a little
Bossa Nova?
(EXCLAlMS)
(SLOW MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(BOTH CHUCKLlNG)
He looks happy.
Yep.
Well, well, well.
Hmm. Boss for. . .
What was it? Oh.
Four-and-a-half hours.
New record. Low.
Previous record,
Henry Rostin.
Boss for nine years,
four months.
And he only left
because he had family
matters to attend to,
and he. . . What?
(MUSlC CONTlNUES PLAYlNG)
DWlGHT: Michael !
(ELEVATOR BELL DlNGS)
l can't help but think
that something we did
made this possible.
Jim dug his own grave,
but maybe we provided
the shovel.
(EXCLAlMS) Temp, l like that.
l'm gonna engrave that
into a piece of wood.
Care to celebrate
with a drink?
l would love to.
(CHUCKLlNG)
Why not?
Because martini bars
are pretentious.
No, thank you.
l'm sorry that
l don't want
farm-boy swill
like you do, you know?
lt is not farm-boy swill.
l will show you.
lt is beet vodka
and it is delicious.
l'm not interested
in anything l have to
make myself.